astraltabletop.com 2019-04-16

# Privacy Policy | Astral TableTop

**Effective date: May 30, 2018**

We at Unicorn Heart Club LLC (“Unicorn”) know you care about how your personal information is used and shared and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. Unicorn recognizes the importance of protecting information collected from users and has adopted this privacy policy to inform users about how Unicorn gathers, stores, and uses information derived from their use of Unicorn products, services and online sites.

By using or accessing the Services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways. 

This policy is current as of its last revision date. However, please note that this policy may be amended from time to time to reflect changes and additions to the privacy policy. Please check back for the most current version before relying on any of the provisions in this privacy policy.

#### Entities Collecting Personal Information

We have appointed a data protection officer (DPO) for Unicorn who is responsible for overseeing questions in relation to this privacy notice. If you have any questions, concerns, or requests about this privacy notice, how we manage your Personal Information, or any other issue relating to your Personal Information, please contact our DPO:

    Unicorn Heart Club LLC
    Attn: Data Protection Officer
    privacy@astraltabletop.com
    268 6th St Fl 3, Jersey City, NJ 07302

#### Collection of Information

By using Unicorn's online sites, products, and services, users agree that Unicorn collects and processes the personally identifiable information (as defined below) they provide by creating a user account, by purchasing or selling subscriptions, or during any exchange with Unicorn in connection with the use of their user account. Unicorn will not share any personally identifiable information with other parties except as described in this policy. Unicorn also processes anonymous data, aggregated or not, in order to analyze and produce statistics related to the habits, usage patterns, and demographics of users as a group or as individuals. Such anonymous data does not allow the identification of the users to which it relates. Unicorn may share anonymous data, aggregated or not, with third parties.

#### Personally Identifiable Information

"Personally identifiable information" is information that can be used to uniquely identify a user such as name, address or credit card number. If you are an EU user, "personally identifiable information" means "personal data" within the meaning of article 2 a) of the Directive 95/46 of 24 October 1995. You may be asked to provide personally identifiable information during the sign in process, and then in connection with the use of Unicorn’s products, services and online sites. While Unicorn collects personally identifiable information on a voluntary basis, for certain products and services Unicorn's collection of personally identifiable information may be a requirement for access to the product or service or to process a user’s order. 

#### Use of personally identifiable information

Personally identifiable information is used internally by Unicorn to deliver, develop and improve products, content and services, to which users have subscribed, and to answer users’ requests. In addition, Unicorn may allow third parties performing services under contract with Unicorn, such as order or payment processors or merchandise warehouse and fulfillment services, located in and outside the European Union, to access and use personally identifiable information, but only to the extent necessary to provide those services. 

Unicorn may use personally identifiable information provided by users to send them information about Unicorn, including news about product updates, contests, events, and other promotional materials, but only if the users agree to receive such communications. Unicorn will not share any personally identifiable information with third parties for marketing purposes without your consent.

When you create a user account, Unicorn collects a user's email address and username, and at the user's option, first and last name. Depending on their settings, users agree that some of this information may be searchable and available to other users within user. Unicorn has no obligation to keep private personally identifiable information that a user makes available to other users via user or other Unicorn software, such as in multiplayer chat or other public functions. 

External websites and companies with links to and from Unicorn's online sites and products may collect personally identifiable information about users when users visit their websites. Third party publishers may also collect personally identifiable information as a requirement of accessing their games or content. Unicorn's privacy policy does not extend to external websites and companies or third party publishers with links to or from Unicorn’s products and online websites or who collect personally identifiable information through their game available on user. Please refer directly to these companies and websites regarding their privacy policies.

Unicorn may release personally identifiable information to comply with court orders or laws that require us to disclose such information. In the event of a reorganization, sale or merger we may transfer personally identifiable information to the relevant third party with the user’s consent if required by law.

#### Children Under The Age of 13

Unicorn will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any person under the age of 13. Unicorn encourages parents to instruct their children to never give out personal information when online. Parents who are concerned about the transfer of personal information from their children may contact us.

#### Cookies and Other Information on a User's Machine

Unicorn’s products, services and sites may employ cookies and other technologies such as web beacons and pixel tags. Cookies are bits of electronic information that can be transferred to a user's hard drive to customize a person's use of a product or online site, keep records of a user's access to an online site or product, or store information needed by the user on a regular basis. Use of cookies is typically associated with websites. For example, when you sign in to user, Unicorn stores your user id and a combination of your IP address and time of login as a cookie on your hard drive. This cookie allows you to move from page to page without having to sign in again on each page. Similarly, if you enter information during your session, such as age verification data, this will be stored as a cookie and you will not have to re-enter such information during that session. We may also use third party web site analytic tools that employ cookies to collect certain non-personally identifiable information concerning use of our websites, such as referring web site addresses, page views and browser types.

However, users can disable cookies by changing their browser settings. 

Unicorn also stores on a user’s hard drive a unique authorization key or CD-Key that is either entered by the user or downloaded automatically during product registration. This authorization key is used to identify a user as valid and allow access to Unicorn's products, services and third party games. This key is necessary for Unicorn to supply any products and services subscribed by users.

Information regarding user billing, a user’s user account, a user’s Internet connection and the Unicorn software installed on a user’s computer is uploaded to the server in connection with the user’s use of user and Unicorn software. Unicorn software automatically generates and submits to Unicorn bug reports upon a crash or other fault in the Unicorn software, services or user games. This automatically generated bug report information may include information about other software or hardware on a user's system. Unicorn does not associate and store the automatically generated bug report information with users’ personally identifiable information. Any bug reporting information manually submitted by users (e.g. through Unicorn's Bug Reporter form) is associated and stored with personally identifiable information sent voluntarily by the user through a bug report.

#### Chat Forums, Etc.

Unicorn's products or services may provide chat, forums, bulletin boards, or instant messaging tools to users. Any information that is disclosed in chat, forums or bulletin boards should be considered public information, and users who message one another may not know each other personally. Unicorn has no obligation to keep private personally identifiable information that a user makes available to other users or the public using these functions. Users should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in public forums. Users should also be aware that game play information disclosed during multiplayer game play (e.g. player name and current player statistics) is public information and may be displayed to other users.

#### Choice/Opt-out

Unicorn gives users the option to receive promotional email communications from Unicorn. Users may opt out of these communications. Instructions for discontinuing receipt of promotional email communications from Unicorn will be provided in email communications to users.

#### Storage and Security of Personally Identifiable Information

Personally identifiable information provided to Unicorn will be collected, processed and stored by Unicorn in the United States. Unicorn has taken reasonable steps to protect the information users share with us, including, but not limited to, setup of processes, equipment and software to avoid unauthorized access or disclosure of this information.

#### Payment Data

Payment processing related to Content and Services and/or physical goods purchased by user is performed by third-party payment vendors Stripe, Google Checkout, and PayPal on behalf of Unicorn depending on the type of payment method used. If your card was issued outside the United States, your payment may be processed via a European acquirer by Stripe, Google Checkout, or PayPal on behalf of Unicorn. For any other type of purchases, payment will be collected by Unicorn directly. In any case, delivery of Content and Services as well as physical goods is performed by Unicorn.

#### Corrections, Updates and Removal of Personally Identifiable Information

Upon request Unicorn will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information. To request this information please contact us at [privacy@astraltabletop.com](mailto:privacy@astraltabletop.com).

If you are concerned about the accuracy of personally identifiable information maintained by Unicorn or wish to review, access, amend or correct it, or would like your personally identifiable information removed from Unicorn's records or otherwise deactivated, please contact us at [privacy@astraltabletop.com](mailto:privacy@astraltabletop.com).

#### Contacting Unicorn

If you have any questions or complaints about this privacy policy, or the privacy practices of Unicorn, please contact us here. You may also contact Unicorn Heart Club LLC at the address below.

Unicorn Heart Club LLC  
268 6th St Fl 3  
Jersey City, NJ 07302  
United States of America

#### Privacy Shield

Unicorn complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. Unicorn has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit [http://www.privacyshield.gov](http://www.privacyshield.gov/).

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Unicorn commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact Unicorn here. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, certain residual claims not resolved by other means may be subject to binding arbitration. In such event, an arbitration option will be made available to you.

The Privacy Shield Principles describe Unicorn's accountability for personal data that it subsequently transfers to a third party agent. Under the Principles, Unicorn shall remain liable if third party agents process the personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless Unicorn proves it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

The Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over Unicorn’s compliance with the Privacy Shield.

 _This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 30, 2018._
